In many programming languages, objects should
be closed when they are no longer needed to
save memory usage on a device from the app.
In file management, files no longer needed
should be closed so that one does not accidentally
alter a file that should not be altered.
Closing a file frees up memory space the file
is taking while in use, thus helping a device
run more efficiently.
Additionally, closing a file often allows
it to be safely modified by other programs.
In the previous topic, we saw how to open
a file.
We will continue going through the process
of working with a file used in game management.
In this version of the file, 312-close, we
have, on line 6, opened the 312-message text
file.
We will eventually write some text to this
file, but I want to ensure that when we are
done with the file, we close it.
Thus, on line 8, I will add this text: message_text.close().
The majority of programming languages use
parentheses for method and function calls
and definitions.
The parentheses serve multiple purposes.
First, it makes functions easily identifiable
and maintains specific syntax.
Second, functions often require arguments—the
values that get passed into the functions—and
parentheses serve as a container for those
arguments.
It's worth noting that not all functions require
arguments, and there are some cases where
functions can be passed as arguments to other
functions without invoking them, without parentheses.
Those exceptions, for example, are in a language
like Structured Query Language or SQL.